ED]
Momochan has never been to a gymnastics club before, and she is not getting enough exercise on a daily basis,
Today, we are here at Yukio Ikeya's gymnastics club.
Please let's start with you.
Yes, hello. I am Yukio Ikeya.
My name is Yukio Ikeya. Pleased to meet you.
Is this your first time? Gymnastics club?
Yes, I have.
You've never done gymnastics before?
Have you ever done mats, vault, operating board?
I have done the vault.
For how long?
I don't know.
About I don't know?
Elementary school?
We had a jumping box in elementary, junior high, and high school.
What? You did it in elementary, middle school, and college?
I didn't go to college.
What about bars?
No bars.
No bars? Really?
You've never done Sac-Hagari?
You know, everyone used to do that when they were little.
No?
No.
Oh, I understand.
Gymnastics has three kinds of gymnastics: mats, vaults, and bars,
There are hundreds of techniques in gymnastics.
Shall we try some of them?
Yes.
Do you know Mr. Yukio Ikeya?
Yes, I do.
Do you know him?
Of course.
Really? You looked him up.
You looked it up and you know about it, don't you?You've looked it up. You know it, don't you?
No, since I was a kid.
What do you mean when you were a kid?
I saw you on TV.
That's great.
But you're such a loud guy.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have to be loud to teach kids, or they don't listen to me.
But when I hear your voice, I don't hear through it.
I can't hear through it. Okay, okay.
I'll make some adjustments.
Thank you for watching.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
No!
I can't believe I'm saying this.
I just want the world to change a little bit.
I want you to change it.
No!
This show is a variety show where Ana-chan tries various things!
Before you start paying attention, you must do the same as you would do for any sporting event.
Preparation exercises.
Uh...
You don't like it?
No, they're injury-prone.
That's why we do them.
Yes, sir.
You look like you hate it.
But you know what?
We're all hard.
Right?
Let's do warm-ups.
Okay.
Well, I guess we're good here.
A little bit here, okay?
Right there.Hey there.
Where are you looking?
You have to look at me.
Let's do what I do.
Okay, then.
I'm going to give you the finger.
Hands and knees first.
Legs are for gymnastics.
They ask you to put your feet in a "goo" position.
When you close your legs, it means "goo".
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
You're not following me at all, are you?
Five.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Okay, now here's the stretchy part.
Spread your legs apart a little bit.
Bend one leg and stretch the other.
Now go deeper.
Again, here's the point.
Put the soles of your feet together.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Put your feet on the floor, right here.
Put your feet on.
Okay, thumbs up, thumbs up, thumbs up.
Oh, that hurts.
What? You hurt yourself?
Okay, work on this.
Press your knees.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Opposite.
Gee, gee, gee, gee
go for this, go for this, go for this
Go for it!Come on.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
There you go.
Now, Sumo wrestler.
Like this, but with the hip joints.
Keep your hips up.
What?
Elbows, elbows, elbows like this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Good luck.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
I know it hurts.
That's how it works. That's why it hurts.
Why does it hurt?
It hurts because it's stretched.
It's a good sign that it's working.
That's a great job on the groin.
Okay, well, you can make your feet a little bit narrower.
Hooray for being the worst.
Hooray.
When you do the hooray, stretch out your elbows.
That's right.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Stretch it out.
Press firmly like this.
Press firmly.
Breathe out and touch the ground without bending your knees
It hurts.
What?
I can't reach.
I can't reach it.
Never.
Really? - Yeah. Okay, well, I don't care if you can't reach it, just put it on.
Exhale, exhale, exhale, exhale.Ha-ha-ha! Breathe in, breathe out, ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha.
What's this for?
What for?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm not doing this for nothing, but for this... calf-joint, thigh-joint, butt-stretch... stretch here, stretch here.
Why are you doing this?
I said it's going to hurt.
I explained it to you, didn't I? You have to do things that hurt to get them soft, okay?
You know how I explain to my kids that injections hurt?
Right? But you don't run away from it, right? There's nothing you can't do, right?
Yeah.
You're going to do it, even though it hurts.
I like needles.
What? That's not what I'm talking about.
It's a different story, but it's the kind of pain that's good for you.
Likewise, if you stretch this, it'll hurt, but if you do it hard, it'll stretch here and feel good afterwards.
Uh...
You know what I mean? It hurts now.
Okay?
Okay, now, bend your back knee this time, but just below your belly button, and then move it forward.
You can look forward, and then you can look backwards from here.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Don't go back.
That's it.
Just a little bit more under the belly button, under the belly button.
Let it out.
It hurts.
You're right, it hurts.
Don't cut it, there's a lot of things that hurt, so don't cut it.
It's okay, take care of it.
Okay? Now we're going to do some forward bends, so please sit with your knees straight.
This is our gymnast, and she's on the athletes' course.
I'm Hana Suzuki, 5th grade.
Hana.
Hana.Hana.
Okay, well, please put it on in front of you for a minute.
Wow!
Like this.
Amazing!
I want to be able to turn like this.
I'll go in front of you.
Try to make a straight line like this
I can't do it.
I can't do it, but you can do it.
And do the bridge.
Yes, I'll do that too.
I won't do it.
I'm not saying I won't do it. I'm saying I'll try.
I'll see if I can do it.
Let's see if you can do this.
Okay, first of all, stretch your knees.
Please sit with your knees straight.
Okay.
Now, in front of you, this in front of you.
Here you go.
Okay.
I'll push.
I haven't pushed yet.
Ow, ow, ow.
I'm not really pushing. Not yet.
I'm just stretching my knee.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch.
No, no, no, I didn't push at all.
It hurts really, really bad.
That's why it's so hard
It hurts so much!
Please tell me where it hurts.
There, on the back of my thighs and...So the shin, the back of the thigh and
And the back of this knee.
back of the thighs and behind the knees.
Okay, well, good luck with that.
Not if this is okay.
It's not about whether it's okay or not.
It's not about whether it's okay or not, it's about getting to the point where it hurts.
It's not about whether it's okay or not, it's about getting to the point where it hurts, okay?
I'm not asking you if you're okay, because you're not doing it.
Here's where it starts to hurt.
I'll be patient. Good luck.
That's good.
I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm dying.
You know, I've never seen anyone die.
Hey.
Here.
If you're hard like that...
When you do something like this, when you run or jump...
When you run or jump...
The back of the leg...
Then, let's start with the legs.
Let's try the side first.
Okay.
A little unnoticed.
Keep it like this and roll it to the side.
Like this.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch.
If you bend your knees, it won't do any good.
Don't bend your knees.
I'll do my best with this.
Here you go.
It hurts.Ouch.
It hurts.
So that's why it's hard.
Against.
It'll feel better afterwards.
It's popular in stretching classes.
That's why you'll feel better afterwards.
After.
Before the end.
Why are you trying to get away?
To the left.
Here.
You're hurting me.
In front.
Here you go.
It's in front.
In front.
It hurts.
It hurts here.
I know it hurts.
I know.
It hurts.
Hang in there.
You have no idea who's watching.
I'm serious.
I'm not moving.
It hurts like hell.
If it hurts, it means
That means it's really hard.
Let's move forward from here.
Here you go.
It hurts.
You're not moving.
It hurts when I laugh.
Don't laugh.Don't laugh.
I'm not moving at all.
I know.
Good luck.
When you get home...
Do it after your bath.
Why do I have to do it?
What's the point of doing it even if it hurts?
There are many reasons.
First of all, you are less likely to get hurt.
And if it's gymnastics...
If it's gymnastics, you'll be better at gymnastics
And you'll be better at any sport.
You know what?
The more flexible your body is, the longer you'll live.
It's a good thing.
From this distance.
I'm not talking loud enough.
Laughing.
I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to the audience.
A little bit.
I'm an idiot.
Laugh at the microphone.
You're laughing.
I'm a big guy to begin with.
I'm going to the bridge.
Oh, no.
Try it and go to sleep.
Lie on your stomach.
Put your feet and hands on the floor.
Raise your stomach.
That's good.
Hmm? How do you do that?
Here, on your back.
Do it?Do it?
Do it?
Here we go. This is how it goes. Ready?
Yo!
It's so heavy.
Are you ready?
More back.
Do it more like a warp.
Bend over. Come on, turn!
Come on, turn!
Oh, you're doing it.
You're not doing it.
It's not working.
Come on.
Yo!
It's so heavy.
So, that's on the way.
It was kind of done.
Not even a little bit done?
No, no, no.
You see the bridge?
The bridge. I want you to be that one.
Come on!
Can you help me with this?
What the hell?
You coming?
What the hell? Do it yourself. let's go!
Gyoon!
Awww!
Masai size tar chan.
I'm sweating all over this.
Why am I sweating?
Why is this so unbearable? I'm flexible.
Okay, let's try this on the mat.
This is actually, uh...This is, in fact.
It's the same yukata they're wearing at the Olympics.
This?
This one.
Let's do some basic moves with it.
It's an easy one.
You can definitely do this.
Let's start with the premise.
The basics
Handstands
Pause
This is a pose from gymnastics.
You do this a lot, right? Have you seen the Olympics?
The Glico.
No, not Glico.
Wait a minute.
That was fun.
Glico, that's for the finish line, that's not the same thing.
Gymnastics teacher pose.
Let's start here.
We're going to start here, hands on the ground.
When you put your hands on the floor, just like in the bridge.
Look at your navel on par.
Put your head back.
Hands in front of you.
That's it.
I did this in elementary school. I did it in elementary school.
I forgot the pause, so you come out of the pause, put your hands on your navel, and look at your navel.
Pause with the back of your head in front of you.
Oh, wow.
Okay, that's good. I got it. Now backwards.
This one's going to be a little harder.
Kneel down, and from here, turn around, keeping your eyes on your belly button.
Pose with your hands pressed down. It's important to keep your hands on the mat.
Yes, on the mat.
Okay, let's try it. Bend your knees.Okay, let's try it. Bend your knees.
Look at the belly button. Hands in the air.
Ready?
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Huh? Wait a minute, please.
Go back, please.
I'm scared.
I'm scared. It's okay.
Be careful.
Yes, yes, yes.
And pause.
Why are you posing?
Okay, here we go.
It gets a little harder.
I'm tired.
Okay, ready?
It's just a touchy-feely moment, Amu.
Okay.
Okay, now stand on your head.
Stand on your head.
Next, hands, hooray, from the side of the ear.
While speaking.
One, two, stop.
And now...
You can't do this.
I'll stop.
That's great.
And...
Clap!
Clap.
Yes, sir.
But Amu will assist you.But Amu will assist you.
First, try standing on your head.
And look at the mat.
Like this. Don't put your head in.
Don't put your head in.
And keep your eyes on the mat.
Keep your body straight.
Do it.
I'll do it.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
I don't care if I die.
I won't let you die. I won't let you die.
I won't let you die. I won't let you die. I won't let you die.
Okay.
Hooray!
Yes, right next to the ear.
And a footstep. A footstep.
A footstep.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Don, don, don!
I'm scared.
Hang in there!
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
Hang in there.
I'm scared. I'm scared. You're not a fish.
Why wow.
What the fuck?
What is it?
What about what?
What?
It was like a fish.
Like a fish.
Like a fish. You've never been upside down.
No, I haven't.not much
Not really.
Yes, I could.
Yes, it's done.
Don.
Come on! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Stretch out your knees! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
And, just jump!
Nice!
Yes, circle! Well done!
It's very important to put pressure on the belly like you just did!
Try it at home!
I don't want to go home!
I want to do some development!
Deployment?
This is what deployment is!
Up here, up here!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God! That's amazing!
I wanna see it again!
Let's go! It's called Hope. She comes running down the runway.
And then he goes up, and then he goes up!
Wow! That's amazing!
This is what we call a development!
Want to try it?
Yes!
But it's easy, so let's do it!
You don't need it!
No, no, no, no, no!
It looks hard!
It's not that hard!
Here we go!
That's the headstand!
Do a handstand from here.
Boom!Boom!
That's what I'm talking about!
It's okay!
You can still do this! It's going to happen!
This is the real thing! Here you go!
Deploy!
Deployment! Try a sequence!
I can do sequences!
You'll be able to do this.
Kiss from there.
And then...
I'm scared.
It's okay.
That's what happens when you bend your knees, right?
That's just stretching it out.
Don't get so drunk.
Do it.
And then, boom, boom, boom, up there.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There you go. There you go.
Now, when you get it up like this, it's like the one I just did.
Don't fall asleep.
Don't get comfortable with Mack.
This is the best place.
No, I know it's the best place, but...
I mean, I know it's the best place, but it's really good, right?
Subscribe to our amateur channel.